<odoo>
    <record model="payroll.compensation.category" id="payroll_compensation_category_0">
        <field name="vertex_id">0</field>
        <field name="name">Cash</field>
        <field name="description">Cash</field>
        <field name="incl_gp_deduction" eval="True"/>
    </record>
    <record model="payroll.compensation.category" id="payroll_compensation_category_1">
        <field name="vertex_id">1</field>
        <field name="name">Group Term Life Over $50000</field>
        <field name="description">IRC section 79 provides an exclusion for the first $50,000 of group-term life insurance coverage provided under a policy carried directly or indirectly by an employer. The imputed cost of coverage in excess of $50,000 must be included in income, using the IRS Premium Table, and are subject to social security and Medicare taxes.
Please update new tax rule and refer detail at www.IRS.gov
        </field>
    </record>
    <record model="payroll.compensation.category" id="payroll_compensation_category_2">
        <field name="vertex_id">2</field>
        <field name="name">Bonus</field>
        <field name="description">Bonus</field>
        <field name="incl_gp_deduction" eval="True"/>
    </record>
    <record model="payroll.compensation.category" id="payroll_compensation_category_3">
        <field name="vertex_id">3</field>
        <field name="name">Stock Options</field>
        <field name="description">Non-qualified Stock Option is a type of employee stock option where you pay ordinary income tax on the difference between the grant price and the price at which you exercise the option.
Please refer new tax rule at www.IRS.gov
        </field>
    </record>
    <record model="payroll.compensation.category" id="payroll_compensation_category_4">
        <field name="vertex_id">4</field>
        <field name="name">Educational Asst (Job Related)</field>
        <field name="description">Expenses paid by an employer for the education of the employee. It defines educationally-related expenses as including tuition, fee, books, supplies and equipment, but does not limit them except for an exclusion of tools and supplies retained by the employee after completion of the course. Job related refers to if it helps the employee maintain or improve skills required for a job and is not limited to a certain dollar amount.
        </field>
    </record>
    <record model="payroll.compensation.category" id="payroll_compensation_category_5">
        <field name="vertex_id">5</field>
        <field name="name">Educational Asst (Non-job Related)</field>
        <field name="description">Expenses paid by an employer for the education of the employee for non job related classes. It defines educationally-related expenses as including tuition, fee, books, supplies and equipment, but does not limit them except for an exclusion of tools and supplies retained by the employee after completion of the course. This has an excludable limit of $5250.
        </field>
    </record>
    <record model="payroll.compensation.category" id="payroll_compensation_category_6">
        <field name="vertex_id">6</field>
        <field name="name">Adoption Assistance</field>
        <field name="description">Employer-provided amounts your employer pays directly to either you or a third party for qualified adoption expenses under a qualified adoption assistance program up to a qualified maximum limit.
        </field>
    </record>
    <record model="payroll.compensation.category" id="payroll_compensation_category_7">
        <field name="vertex_id">7</field>
        <field name="name">Qualified Moving Expense Reimbursements</field>
        <field name="description">Reimbursed and employer-paid qualified moving expenses (those that would otherwise be deductible by the employee) paid under an accountable plan are not includible in an employee's income unless you have knowledge the employee deducted the expenses in a prior year.
        </field>
    </record>
    <record model="payroll.compensation.category" id="payroll_compensation_category_8">
        <field name="vertex_id">8</field>
        <field name="name">Van Pool &amp; Transit Passes</field>
        <field name="description">Qualified mass transit expenses include transit passes for mass transportation to and from work. Qualified amounts include the costs of any pass, token, fare card, voucher, or similar item entitles the employee to use mass transit for the purpose of traveling to and from his or her place of work. The mass transit can be a public system, or a private enterprise provided by a company or individual who is in the business of transporting people in what is know as a commuter highway vehicle. The vehicle needs to seat at least 6 adults not including the driver.
This is employer-financed expense: company pays directly for the cost of an employee's transit.
        </field>
    </record>
    <record model="payroll.compensation.category" id="payroll_compensation_category_9">
        <field name="vertex_id">9</field>
        <field name="name">Qualified Parking</field>
        <field name="description">Qualified parking expenses include the following costs: Parking a vehicle in a facility that is near the employee's place of work, parking at a location from where the employee commutes to work (for example, the cost of parking in a lot at the train station).
This is employer-financed expense: company pays directly for the cost of an employee's parking.
        </field>
    </record>
    <record model="payroll.compensation.category" id="payroll_compensation_category_10">
        <field name="vertex_id">10</field>
        <field name="name">Reported Tips</field>
        <field name="description">Tips employee reports as received</field>
    </record>
    <record model="payroll.compensation.category" id="payroll_compensation_category_11">
        <field name="vertex_id">11</field>
        <field name="name">125HSA</field>
        <field name="description">Health Savings Account (HSA) is a tax-advantaged medical savings account available to taxpayers in the United States who are enrolled in a high-deductible health plan (HDHP). These contributions may be made pre-taxed under a Sec 125 Cafeteria Plan.
        </field>
    </record>
    <record model="payroll.compensation.category" id="payroll_compensation_category_12">
        <field name="vertex_id">12</field>
        <field name="name">HSA</field>
        <field name="description">Health Savings Account (HSA) is a tax-advantaged medical savings account available to taxpayers in the United States who are enrolled in a high-deductible health plan (HDHP).
        </field>
    </record>
    <record model="payroll.compensation.category" id="payroll_compensation_category_14">
        <field name="vertex_id">14</field>
        <field name="name">409A Distribution</field>
        <field name="description">Section 409A Non-qualified Deferred Compensation Plan income distribution taxability rules. 
        </field>
    </record>
    <record model="payroll.compensation.category" id="payroll_compensation_category_15">
        <field name="vertex_id">15</field>
        <field name="name">ER STD 125 plan</field>
        <field name="description">Short Term Disability - payments made within 6 months. Benefits and premium paid by the employer
        </field>
    </record>
    <record model="payroll.compensation.category" id="payroll_compensation_category_16">
        <field name="vertex_id">16</field>
        <field name="name">ER LTD 125 plan</field>
        <field name="description">Long Term Disability -  payments made after 6 months. Benefits and premium paid by the employer
        </field>
    </record>
    <record model="payroll.compensation.category" id="payroll_compensation_category_17">
        <field name="vertex_id">17</field>
        <field name="name">Agent STD 125 plan</field>
        <field name="description">Short Term Disability - payments made within 6 months. Benefits and premium paid by the employer but administered by an Agent agent bears no insurance risk.
        </field>
    </record>
    <record model="payroll.compensation.category" id="payroll_compensation_category_18">
        <field name="vertex_id">18</field>
        <field name="name">Agent LTD 125 plan</field>
        <field name="description">Long Term Disability - payments made after 6 months. Benefits and premium paid by the employer but administered by an Agent.
        </field>
    </record>
    <record model="payroll.compensation.category" id="payroll_compensation_category_19">
        <field name="vertex_id">19</field>
        <field name="name">3rd Party STD 125 plan</field>
        <field name="description">Short Term Disability - payments made within 6 months. Benefits paid by a Third Party with premium paid by employer, Third Party is paid an insurance premium and assumes the risk
        </field>
    </record>
    <record model="payroll.compensation.category" id="payroll_compensation_category_20">
        <field name="vertex_id">20</field>
        <field name="name">3rd Party LTD 125 plan</field>
        <field name="description">Long Term Disability - payments made after 6 months. Benefits paid by a Third Party with premium paid by employer.
        </field>
    </record>
    <record model="payroll.compensation.category" id="payroll_compensation_category_21">
        <field name="vertex_id">21</field>
        <field name="name">Golden Parachute</field>
        <field name="description">In general it is a payment made under a contract entered into by a corporation and key personnel. Under the agreement, the corporation agrees to pay certain amounts to its key personnel in the event of a change in ownership or control of the corporation. 
        </field>
    </record>
    <record model="payroll.compensation.category" id="payroll_compensation_category_22">
        <field name="vertex_id">22</field>
        <field name="name">Domestic Partner Benefit Non-Dependent</field>
        <field name="description">The value of employer provided health plan coverage for employee's and any person other than a qualified dependent. 
        </field>
    </record>
    <record model="payroll.compensation.category" id="payroll_compensation_category_23">
        <field name="vertex_id">23</field>
        <field name="name">Domestic Partner Benefit Dependent</field>
        <field name="description">The value of employer provided health plan coverage for employee's, employee's spouses and dependents.
        </field>
    </record>
    <record model="payroll.compensation.category" id="payroll_compensation_category_24">
        <field name="vertex_id">24</field>
        <field name="name">Adult Child Health Coverage</field>
        <field name="description">Affordable Health Care Act taxability rules for employer provided health benefits for children under age 27
        </field>
    </record>
    <record model="payroll.compensation.category" id="payroll_compensation_category_25">
        <field name="vertex_id">25</field>
        <field name="name">Meals for the convenience of ER</field>
        <field name="description">Meals furnished for the employer's convenience and on the employer's premises.</field>
    </record>
    <record model="payroll.compensation.category" id="payroll_compensation_category_26">
        <field name="vertex_id">26</field>
        <field name="name">Military Differential Pay</field>
        <field name="description">Differential wage payments. Differential wage payments are any payments made by an employer to an individual for a period during which the individual is performing service in the uniformed services while on active duty for a period of more than 30 days and represent all or a portion of the wages the individual would have received from the employer if the individual were performing services for the employer.
        </field>
    </record>
    <record model="payroll.compensation.category" id="payroll_compensation_category_28">
        <field name="vertex_id">28</field>
        <field name="name">Severance Pay</field>
        <field name="description">The compensation that an employer provides to an employee who has been laid off, whose job has been eliminated, who through mutual agreement has decided to leave the company, or who has parted ways with the company for other reasons.
        </field>
    </record>
    <record model="payroll.compensation.category" id="payroll_compensation_category_29">
        <field name="vertex_id">29</field>
        <field name="name">Severance Pay required by law</field>
        <field name="description">The compensation that an employer provides to an employee who has been laid off, whose job has been eliminated, who through mutual agreement has decided to leave the company, or who has parted ways with the company for other reasons.
Use this if you are required by law or contract to provide severance pay.
        </field>
    </record>
    <record model="payroll.compensation.category" id="payroll_compensation_category_30">
        <field name="vertex_id">30</field>
        <field name="name">Deceased Worker Pay</field>
        <field name="description">The final paycheck for an employee who has passed within the same year. May include accrued but unused vacation, sick time, Paid Time Off (PTO), and other leave in accordance with state law. Final wages paid within the same calendar year that the employee has died are not subject to Federal Income Tax (FITW), but are subject to FICA and FUTA.
        </field>
    </record>
    <record model="payroll.compensation.category" id="payroll_compensation_category_31">
        <field name="vertex_id">31</field>
        <field name="name">Clergy Housing Allowance</field>
        <field name="description">The clergy housing allowance is a portion of a pastor's income designated specifically by a church or denominational authority to cover his or her housing expenses. These expenses include, but are not limited to the following: Down payment on a home. Mortgage payments. Real estate taxes. Property insurance. Utilities. Furnishings and appliances (including repairs). Structural repairs. Yard maintenance. Snow removal. Trash pickup.
To be eligible, the pastor must be a “minister of the gospel” and be ordained, licensed, or commissioned by a church, convention, or association of churches. The minister's employing organization must officially designate the allowance as a housing allowance before paying it to the minister.
        </field>
    </record>
    <record model="payroll.compensation.category" id="payroll_compensation_category_32">
        <field name="vertex_id">32</field>
        <field name="name">Expanded Family and Medical Leave</field>
    </record>
    <record model="payroll.compensation.category" id="payroll_compensation_category_33">
        <field name="vertex_id">33</field>
        <field name="name">Emergency Paid Sick Leave</field>
    </record>
</odoo>
